Man. Married
man. The for.
The boss.
The. Boss
the other.
One.
Well they're way off but turn down the
next boss my friends or I'll get up for.
A Walk To thing else. You.
See you know we had
a. Piece. Of you would have know what
I might be able to help you out.
With
a result like I don't like the right alone
at night and one of those guys got to
talk right. My party's got to
keep coming but I have nobody to.
Blame maybe I couldn't have I don't say.
Much About My Mother taught me never to
speak to strangers. So OK OK Don't get so I
try to be so let's. They
glamorous the chase for
a dime what it. Says
on the quiet of the time Joe was the
thing that was wrong with this.
Done with you. Know and
don't rush me where you.
Turned off the internet thing are what
you're now you know what they do that
because they give things you know I got no
friends are when I'm out I was minding.
The free country and I say whatever I
want to. Show them you don't like it you
don't have to listen to and you can leave
there any time you want to appeal to the
I'm sorry first good piece played tonight
you don't like it some people just think
got any good taste.
I was always that rotten too. But when
you're around beating in my head never
letting up. If you ever
want to forget anything
if you ever want to cut away a P.C.
a Memory or blot it out you can't. No
matter how hard you try you can change the
scenery but sooner or later you'll get
it with a perfume with somebody will say
a certain phrase or maybe hum
something. Like that can. You believe
that you're in love with me and used to
love that song on one of the custom spec
you know break of dawn of the
New York I can't remember
a night when I didn't get at least three
requests for us. Too. She was always
telling it to. Those with an.
Emphasis on Mad Men you
couldn't move I can't. Move in
love with some. Fluid.
On your mind. And in me
you're in love with me
the best. Long way.
From. Just hurt him. To merlin.
On the cost of our lives.
The good I'm not the one I
can't be big news let me.
It wasn't much of a club really you know
the kind of joint where you could have
a sandwich and
a few drinks and run interference for
your girl on the dance floor. One of the
piano in there every night from eight until
the place closed up which usually meant
for the morning
a good job as Jobs went on stage. It
was still made working there
a little like working in heaven. But how
we felt about each other well there was
nothing very unusual in that I was an
ordinary healthy guy and she was. Ordinary of
the girl when you add those two together
you get an ordinary healthy romance which
is the old story sure but somehow the
most wonderful thing in the world.
ELEANOR HALL I was
a pretty lucky guy. Just
about
a risky I think it's beautiful if you're
going to make kind of whole yet out. As
a janitor I make my debut
in the basement of
a plane it would be better down but you
mustn't give up hope I someday yes some day
I don't get out right is first
the mean time of the strap.
Or or.
The new.
I get somebody has got
a big sell out as is my appetite
with the bad stuff called Ok.
I can't damage was that down
to see that jump night trying
a party know what drugs that are like drown.
That was the matter with you and I go
on and that's the third time you start to
tell me something and stop. Should have
any secrets major the soup actually going
to make withering in the mice is you and
me repeat Yes that's right in the bush
league I don't get you we've been struck out
. On
a way to talk down but you want to marry
me I love you you know I do and I want to
marry you but but not now
only after even. Sunday I'm
going away. I know you think it's silly
that's why I hesitated to say but I'm going
to California I want to try my luck
because. It's the most stupid thing I ever
heard of but you know millions of people
out there every year wind up publishing
cuspidors about you had better send you
thought if you don't think I have any
talent it has nothing to do with this of
a town all right maybe but what about me
in the middle of the year that you're
putting up all our plans
we may not be just
a few years it won't be that long
but you love me. You know why do.
I call to see my friends I'm home when. I
was got all the time in the world settle
down. Pretty girl I want
to have doing things and.
I have I had thought of being so far away
from you but we'll be together again
someday. Maybe you'll decide to
come out to dinner on the lawn.
Aren't you going to keep
a good night. Sure on
a. Night.
Why. Why.
Why.
They rather get hit the jackpot
this time and Max thanks.
For one the strong end
of the attempt but after
a week when I couldn't get very
excited what did I ask myself why is
a paper calling the Germans
couldn't buy anything I wanted one.
And I thought of something.
On distance and I put a call
through the Los Angeles. R.V.
Harby H A R P E Y the numbers crest
is six five seven two three.
I want to this is out Oh baby it's great
to hear from you too was there you do
to Carolyn I thought I'd go batty without
you I just had. There we're going to
hash slinger she honey that's tough guys
out in Hollywood on the real thing when
it's right in front of them you just take
it out Sue baby keep going around us
casting offices I'm sure you'll
click out. Now don't try to
stop me just expect me to train when I
was train plane bus magic carpet I'll be
there I have to cross at the travel by pogo
stick and then. Let's get married right
away. Back to stuff that's
what I want to hear you say.
Well good bye for now.
I'll be seeing you so.
Home The only way I could cross country I'm
right but even after hiking everything
I owned he had no money to eat. Money. You
know what that is the stuff you never
have enough
a little green things with George Washington's
picture that meant slaves for commit
crimes or die for and. It's the stuff
that has caused more trouble in the world
than anything else we have and it's simply
because it's too little of and. Least I
had to live. So it was me for the fun.
Of
a Gemini strike and. It's not much fun believe
me. Oh yeah I know all about how it's
an education I get it made
a lot of people and all that but me from
now on I'll take my education in college
and P.S.
Sixty two or us and the dollar
ninety eight stamps any less. Coming
writes may save your bus fare but it's
dangerous. You never know what's in store
for you in the squealer breaks. If only I
had known what I was getting into then in
Arizona. And found out the facts make.
It OK let us know that you
know that our. Families
in the middle of.
The new you know Emily Post want to write
a book of rules for guys coming right.
Because. That is now you never know what's
right what you. Wrote along for
a little while either want to sing. Live
in that. I never want to see the strange
people driving cars. Into
You can never tell if
a guy wants to talk. A lot of right have
been cut short because of the. News so I
kept my mouth shut until he started
opening up. At me that little box nickel
probably about. All the way it would.
If I had gone L.A.
. Really traveling as yeah but
I don't expect to make it for
a couple of years at the rate I've been
going right much like that here all bad not
many people stop for a
guy these days but I'm
a stick up maybe the gap I'm
out. By about it from New York.
Or LA at this time I'm on the way.
Right sort of Los Angeles. And drive
a car sure I'll be entire let me
know. I'll and. I guess at least
an hour for it was the most expensive right
and it would get the puppy red lines
about
a quarter of an inch apart. The most to see
me looking at them and he said. Beauties
are they. Going to be skies and
they. Want to know whatever
it was must have been pretty big and vicious
to done that at all costs. I was tough
on the most dangerous animal in a
row a woman. Much been targets made
a spike of us the boy. Said it was
a draw. You know the one of the yellow
things that. I tossed out of the car.
Wrong the left to
a committee expected to be nice to
luncheon. At the all that kind of dame
summarized Sunday school
teaches. A little which. Was the
village was right listen for Guy. Me It
was my book the horses around race tracks
as I was twenty. And on
a million things like. To
make him. Stop the car
open the door. Get on the Duffy
system like old. As that was done I.
Want to see
a real sky get all over
the. Well. I got that when.
I would ask in the coolest dad on
a couple of Franco-Prussian say
it was some of the loafers like
a ration. Out one day and the kid
and I took all that was around at
a tool. Pretty make. Section set and
let it yeah I can see that.
You know that box again with
a. Pain
made me lose my head I guess I began slashing.
For I knew what I put the other kids
I. Was. Just the next to the
coolest job kids I got scared
this that I was gonna run away from home.
Oh man I almost caught me when I was back
in my dad's. The bloody rag I had wrapped
around my wrist Betancourt is attention
to see the bundle to show. I
prayed and when he was calling for
a doctor. I was fifteen sixteen
years ago I have been home since.
Well on average by the seven by the.
Brother was I I had anything in my stomach
for hours. Getting without knowing in the
pit of my belly I didn't want to be in
too big
a rush to put on the big banks. First I had
to make sure this guy knew the score so
I got him down on the right to get to
Hollywood. Our Way down here for it was just
his money don't worry about paying for the
damage on the and that's what Haskell
not another you make it first then maybe
you can do the same to make money. I don't
make the list because by Wednesday of all
this money so I don't need an antibiotic
of stardom if I might just make it all
right. He did most of the talking during the
half hour we were in the place. He rambled
on about his old man we haven't heard
from since he ran away as
a kid now we happen to be
a comic book it's not about how I got roped
in Miami one ranks big man I cleaned up
my box idea like that it was tough luck and
I suppose I missed my guy you just wait
and brought back the fire next season with
all kinds of Jack your life must think
about another. One Else
and thanks I have plenty.
Of. That check this if it's.
Just
a Mr James the people to thank you said
Call again the wait now Saif when we finish
work. Check.
The Globe on that night what we
have to scrap like a lot. After
a while I began to get sleepy.
I was happy. To not be was do
again
a long trip was practically over and had
been no more going to get down the concrete
. I began to think of a few
years. Which is good in
a good writer but it brought
it in with the. Mine. Was
a nice thing to fit into. Amazing what
a full belly can do here magination. Why
don't you. Walk. In warrior that you.
Will move on. It
was why I was. Bullshit.
Where in law was. An
aide.
To ask us. To have. To
have a wake up it's frightening
to think we had a staff but
a top. Perhaps
once upon
a pop. It
open at them thanks Mark. But from then
on something else stepped in and shown to
be off to
a different definition. Of when
I spoke of the Met. Perhaps
but what's the matter you hurt.
Your purpose to have to. Start.
Alice. But I know what you're going to
him maybe before you open your mouth you
going to tell me you don't believe my story
about let's go die give me that don't
make me laugh expression on
your smug face. I saw what.
I was in for would believe he fell out
of the car might have spoken to which of
course he couldn't even he was where I
can come over the head Frisco Yes I was.
Instinct told me to run and I realized it
was called lots of people back down the
road to get in a pint at gas
station guy and we could work in
a worse part then try to explain why I'd
be the. Next possibility was to sit tight
until the truth from the cops but
it would be crazy if we have
a picture not in my head of abuse. So what
else was it to do the kind of body kit
we. Could cause and what human ecology
would be like I'm looking at Tombstone.
Man's.
Hand.
My idea was to come in with fresh paint to
rub it but then I remember that even if
I only drove the car for one hundred miles
or so I would be money for gas. Besides
it was stupid of me to leave all that
money and. Not only that I don't take
a driver's license because I was stuck for
some. I'd like to think about that time
I'd done just what the police would say I
did even if I did. I called the owner of
such an expensive car when everything
went. Up with an excess cash.
They you this your car and
you know better leave
a car the wheel can't wait the middle
road that's the way accidents happen I'm
sorry officer I'm just putting up my top I
think the next time I think I'll let you
go now the watchers step in
the future I know there's
a lovely Christmas card comparison
and while we have plenty of backup.
That's nothing particularly
as rock. They found
a dead man on the go enough to beat me.
As I drove off and still right. The drop
straight down the windshield right here.
I kept imagining I was being followed and
I could hear sirens back in the distance
. Just how long it took me to cover the
sixty odd miles of the California state
line I don't know I was on track of time
for the rain and stopped in the sun was
not my fault I suspect they didn't.
Read any principles to post any
livestock or poultry. Actually or
registration and grab it like. Anything in
the baggage compartment is thank you.
Charles Haskell if you engage thirty brown
eyes dark hair and
a fine Mark. You child has killed Union
if I remember if you going to stay with
thirty days you take out California plates
all right off to blow up in the sea the
short. Psych exam announced.
The Dr any final announcement Hopson Oh
crap I knew I had to hit the hay and get it
right. I was dead.
In ten minutes.
And. Something. That I didn't. Know many
students know.
The in. Was there it's the
metal jacket and clean.
Later. And
a half hour. No
. Move forward.
There was no time to lose and every minute
I had to be trials Haskell was dangerous
not have to be trials has no until I got
some city where I could leave the car and
be swallowed up. That
been driving the cars five San
Bernardino even DOS Angeles in
a little town I might be noticed but in
the city I should be safe enough. Then
after I dish the car I could go on to say.
But those five minutes at the state line
made me realize it might be a good idea
to find out a little bit about Mr S.
. And if anybody asked me questions I could
get the right answer. The first thing I
found out was that I had seven hundred
sixty eight dollars. This was
a lot of jack but believe me with
a kind of money I'd rather not have. And
then I found out from
a letter Haskell was carting around in
his bag when he wasn't the open hand and
easygoing big shot went around buying
dinners for Strange Attractors where I got
done reading and I saw him more as
a child. It was written to his old man in
California when he hadn't seen in so many
. In it has got holes in the sails
of him though I was saying.
It was easy to see where it has collapsed
back to raise the nose stakes for
a book in Miami. By Rocky his old man.
That was about all I found out from his
affect and it was enough. I told myself
maybe old man Haskell was lucky his son
kicked off. He would never know
it but it saved him from taking
a flyer and sacred literature
a preferred. When in
the.
Infant and. In the in.
The loop. You hear want to
desert center up hold up
a water. There when the woman. In
line say you know I want
to you want to ride.
In.
In. All. In.
All.
The in.
A bygone. After me by surprise
I turned my head the girl.
Was facing straight ahead so I couldn't see
her eyes she was young I had more than
twenty four. Man she looked as if
she'd just been thrown up a crummy
a freight train in the world. And yet in
spite of this I got the impression that he
was. Not the beauty of
a movie actress mind you but the beauty you
dream about when you're with your wife
but
a natural human. If you do this almost
calmly because it's all real. Then suddenly
she turned a face up watched
a. Sense was L F. L is another.
But to say nothing just thinking about
people get the top of the till and then. But
your name is coming there are
still on your level Los Angeles.
Where you come from back then
they don't know. Oh sure Phoenix
looks like it's going to screw up and the
girls panics that bad girl most of them
pretty tired because she promised sleep
not twenty minutes going to the car. I
sprung up at rest you can ponder on my guest
I didn't like that product much but in
winter I. Was into this girl's No worries
I've gotten over the funny feeling I had
which was which I would doubtless just
by jangled nerves with her eyes closed
Nestor song out of. Steam. And instead
of this my carer I began to feel sorry.
For kit probably had had
a rough time of. Washing and. Why was
she going to Los Angeles where she
come from the first place the
only thing I knew about it was in
a. Hospice made any difference
a few hours more would be
a holiday I forget where I parked the car
and look up to. This nightmare of being
a dead man. Same as well it was no business
of mine where did you think about.
Playing to leave the owner of this car
you're not fooling anyone fucking belongs to
a guy named Haskell that's not you Mr you're
out of your mind that's my name child
perhaps going through
my driver's ed is not
a trauma as an act of well it only makes
it worse it just so happens I wrote to
Charlie I have come all the way from the
way the ANA He. The POTUS report you wrote
so hard and it all came back to. The
part about do with scars and scratches.
No doubt about it girl most people women
have to let mention just the past me while
I slept around. While I'm white
I guess was close. To having.
That has a guy wasn't dead. He was a stressed
out different color than me I was on
a college he was sitting right there in
the car laughing like mad really hot and.
Well it was nothing I could. Hear
a whatever name was it was just my luck
picking her up on the row. In the bin Helen
Mary or Evan or room. Had to be the very
last person I should ever met. That's like
. Whichever way you turn
a sticks out of what tripped. A
girl or everything but she didn't believe
my story should have saved my breath
that's
a great accomplice story I heard somebody
fell out of it because thankfully I think
it tucked away in the same effect I've been
around and I know wrong guy when I see
one but you do look at him
with a wrench Now wait
a minute what I told you was true you see
that's why I had to do it you think I
killed Well
a couple of not so to yeah well maybe they
still think so. I think you so sure are
sad about this girl I'm innocent and your
break for you. That won't do me any good
having
a pension I've got no friends of mine
now that wonder why there isn't. Don't
thank me yet I'm not through with you by
a long shot let's see that roll. Is
that all that collapse is enough you know
I thought the at Molineux that I know if
you can search me the couple not on you
well maybe I will look back. He told me he
was going to three thousand
dollars on the horse a paradise
a clown with the Santa Anita It was pretty
along about three hundred maybe two or
three bucks three hundred
it was a piece of cheese
a big mistake don't try and tell me anything
about Charlie Haskell remember I know
him better than you'll be
OK that you knew he was
a four flusher that explains it three
grand that I'm not so sure he didn't have
that three grand Why should I believe
you you've got all the earmarks of
a keeper now wait
a minute keep proving you killed him but
two cents I change my mind attorney and I
don't like to ride on I don't get so I'm
not getting so I just remember those folks
around here if you shut up and don't give
me any arguments you'll have nothing to
worry about but if you act wise well Next
you'll stop at the jail cell back it'll
give you the big. Thing that you don't know
what's cookin to humans I think a C.F.L.
Is young and you wind up sniffing that
perfume that are alone I had the freedom
murder is I'm not
a murderer of course and not as go knock
his own head off to jail I thought I'd
just like I told you many make your presence
his belongings are explaining why I
was there that doesn't make a
difference one way or another I'm not
a morning I like Tesco even less than I
like you I started to what do you mean
scratches on his wrist or I scratched
him. So you did. So here I do
drive the car
a little way maybe in San Bernardino and
then later you are going to sell as well
as you think I'm crazy somebody else's car
we all want to do is leave it somewhere
and forget I ever saw it
not only don't you have
a newsgroup like it don't have any
brains I don't get yours maybe it's
a good thing you met me you know that got
yourself caught sure why you don't don't
you know what that automobile always
Reitman best against. The cops find
a cop then they get serious they wonder
where the owner is so all right they don't
trace half the trace you never thought
of. The only safe way to get rid of
a current seller to what you are getting
registered under new name they stop at the
next store I want to get up on to
some shop or we had alley. To find
a place of drop you off think it played or
not but don't you have gotten into From
now on you when I like the Siamese twins
Everett your way I don't get the point the
point I want you get lost not going to
be that that's what you're afraid of not
that you're not going to fix yourself
because you don't get caught by course your
interest wouldn't be financial or do
what you want to small percentage of the
profits Well now that you
and spend time going are
a few hundred percent of the
fine I'm really I thought for
a moment you're going to take it all out
of one of the I hope. You are as they were
in Hollywood I was recognizing places to
admit. Struck me that far from being at
the end of the trip there was
a greater distance between Sue and me
than when I started out. Here I wasn't
kidding with the Chinese
twins correct she rented
a little apartment as Mrs Charles Haskell.
And I object to this she explained it
was on account of the car dealer might
think something was funny because in front
of her using different names.
And sweet home you know. Not bad either.
Case isn't it down there I haue taken
that yeah. Very stuffy if you.
Keep the one that shot OK. They all
crawled out stance or there's a fall of
a sinus stuff.
Out of work. I invented it.
A joint one can have everything.
I'm certain of after I don't know
why but I figured you would be.
Wildland air feels good to be clean
again. I'm assuming and I'm finding.
You much. Knowledge arrives in exactly the
way you keep your school the section.
I wish that guy with the sex
would give up. To marry.
To get. A little. Much of
freedom I think you up
on. I didn't want to get drunk
and involved. Obvious or
is rather you got yourself into this thing.
You should be grateful I'm not turning
you in. Life I wasn't
a regular you'd be in the pen this minute
then photographing up and it would be in
pushed around by the cops. Such
or get rid of that long pause.
Is your conscience bothering you.
It isn't what's worse that's there. Is
definite almost around to bring him back.
Anyway I never could understand this worrying
about something that's over and done
with I'm up there for the last
time I didn't kill it was
a sick man knew he would die before he fell
out of the car I don't know Cheri type
of age. Most. Of the like it sociable.
It didn't kill him.
Thanks.
Or at
a liquor Robert. Yeah. Too bad I
felt like getting typed and I well
I think you succeeded and mark time as
a prima donnas courses that. I want to get
tied by but if you've got to get tight
about oh I don't feel saying. You
should have my worries find your troubles
I'd stay sober and I've got the key to
that door. Yes. If you're
right I'm always rise. And I don't like
your attitude Robards on some other
things I don't like. Lies like
a ballgame you gotta take
a swing at whatever comes along
before you wake up and it's
a nice ending I do read this and that such
a deal ROBERTS It was bellyache thinking
that these aliens were trying to make the
things that maybe that's what's wrong
with the whole world get the perception
people call themselves out trying to buck
fate at thank you for instance you're
lucky to be alive I suppose ASCO it's
open your door if they play and I've now
think of that. You think
of I'm tired as plenty of
people die in this minute I would give
anything to trade places with you. I know
what I'm talking about. I'm not so sure
at least they know they're done for an
artist but wondering if they are.
You'll find lots of these Thanks pal.
We all know we're going to
kick off some day it's only
a question of when. But what got us on
this subject anyway will be discussing
politics next. Year. Or you had the butts.
On the table sack of.
What each other what conversation for
a couple of hours long every five minutes
one of us is wishing we had another
bottle or radio something to read.
Then finally ran out of chat.
I know it's only eleven o'clock and I want
to get up early to make the rounds used
car but now are about that got all the
time in the world maybe you have to do you
think I want to stay cooped up this place
any longer than I have to your back is
not
a bad place they funny for they get like
this in the you're going to like it it was
a wrist. Slap look are
you going to mean comes want to do something
fun and be honest with Camille said.
Somebody you know. Dana
died of consumption.
But to be
a break for you if I did kick up. Before
you will ask or tell and because. I don't
want to see anybody die. Not even me.
Especially not you one person died in the
if you did. So I need. You to like me to.
Like you. I love you. My favorite
sport is being kept prisoner.
After we sell the car you got
a bike for all I get not until then. I'm
going to be.
Good night Robert don't try to sneak away
during the night all the doors are locked
anyway I got in the morning I'll apply the
police that the young man worry and I
want to spy. Punk and I I don't that portable
back into one comfortable for you I'm
going to sleep over the I'm.
The guy.
You. Fix.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
No. Not to town. Tomorrow.
FACE. This work fiction I would fall out
with Mary or make a respectable woman on
the ground she'd make some supreme class
a sacrifice for me. Too and
I would call a little over
a grave make some crack about there's good
knowledge. But there are unfortunately
was just as rap in the morning as she'd
been the night before. All right all right
I'm common parents all of them. So what
the dealer will be there all day I'll be
there out here too with us but
wait that long shot you make like
a husband. Wow you are right it was
a it sure do but let's go let's go let's
go live to ninety five bucks and two hours
to fair and bacon all you can
say is let's go. Come on.
We've had
a few used car lots last night down this
way why do you think we can get this heat
I don't know why they let me handle
everything. They can get around I don't know
but don't worry I'll squeeze as much out
of this guys I can either go cheap without
a problem I think we're still in the car
and listen don't make any slips and call
me Robin Cook I don't need you to tell me
that you better just sit by and keep your
mouth remember we're both in the
soup anything happens to get
a surprise you're my wife or I have. Not
after the day of clothes Let's go back to
that place on Hollywood Boulevard where I
saw the car jacking I was after the deals
cause I'm Sam goodbye to you that's right
I forgot I guess I'm getting kind of used
to you. That's a habit you can start break
and try this place in the middle of
a block.
That's what I do for you
where interested in selling
a car if the price is right. Well if it's
a good mechanical condition it should be
broke for about sixteen hundred. Twenty
take
a look at this motor sixteen
hundred Are you kidding. Well
maybe eight hundred fifty the parlay to go
for eight hundred fifty I reckon collect
the insurance for. It. I did it for a shit
a lot of drive.
Well the mechanic inspected the car we
had. Last we were all worn out we had to
compromise his price. Ok to
deal with I was trying to papers I have
the ownership papers I'm here with me. In
the meantime you painted
a compartment maybe some
stuff in it right. Here
in.
New York. But you bought the car in Miami.
And I wanted to buy the insurance we
need to have a transfer to cancel
a kind of insurance you have missed
and. I know what the person or.
I don't see any Surely you know what type
of insurance you carry in the car the
name of the company. Yeah but well if
you'll just tell me the name of the company
ID very glad to take care of all the details
well look trying to impress us not you
as well though we're not selling
the American way to make
a special Come on what's the matter change
your mind yes I'm sorry I guess I have
one very nice coat. And.
Got me out of
a tight spot but I still don't understand
all this you know well man and I almost
threw away all my eighteen fifties the
receipts to the car doesn't look for as much
as I thought when I'm selling a
car you want to keep but now wait
a minute there you said yourself I wouldn't
be safe until the car was in someone
else's name and I could be free of
this mess when I go that's just
a product you're not telling. At the time
and that's going to pull in AM GOING TO
BUY NOW explain what is another
one of your brilliant ideas.
If you can make mine
a ham sandwich and coffee and do you
think I don't get the same. Things you.
Get there's been pretty patient so far
I've done everything asked me to do but no
more shot of it taken has cost money you
can have the dough we get from selling the
car but you're not going to keep me a
prisoner good thing I bought the paper take
a look at that there I'm anomalies.
No. No I want to I guess you will think
I'm crazy to possible like. These men.
Doesn't want to. Know what could
possibly get away with an act like that
be wise to me in
a minute don't be. Looking up like you the
same color in the same building see I
was close to the consumer tells me for
a while I'll go up there but I think
a father knows his own son and it must be
other relatives the father will have to
know you well well it isn't the ghost he's
an old geezer any will pull through and
as far as the doctors are concerned they
haven't thing in fifteen or twenty is. A
I'm not hungry. And I won't do it it's not
as tough as it sounds remember you've
got all kinds of enough occasion his car
letters like I could never get away with
it just
a brief thing I've ever heard the old boy
has and that tells But on the paper their
personal fortunes are settled over fifty
million he'll leave plenty I tell you
maybe cut office and how do we know I don't
care if I want have anything to do with
it. I think you will appear I'll
do anything within reason but not
that so forget it find yourself another
stooge jokes. So that's it for the rest
your life is Charley Haskell you can take
your inheritance and go away and I worry
about the results like this game and wondering
where your next meal's going to drum
think about that Roberts there are these
you're talking to about and the suspect
that you take with you show I know we're
both alike born the same God I think it
easy for people around here you know when
you talk. Of legal theory that all men
has posted on your show and I can make
New York people think. No suppose he
does and he well I know it well something
tells me. But as much as I insisted I
would have no right to risk there was taking
it for granted I would. Neither of us
got our mind on the cards we played that
night I knew we were just trying to kill
time between newspaper edition. This was
a death watch worker. Maybe it was for me
too to realize I'm caught I want to know
where I got the car and
stuff and I have me on
a murder charge guess Marjorie will get
caught right now because if I'm caught and
she realize you'll be up to.
A tame climbs I mean. How to
Live the out if you'll be out eight hundred
fifty dollars what I've got in the car
really really an awful chump you threw
away all that don't want to does the long
shot let me sell the bus tomorrow with the
money I'll bring in what you've already
got
a clever kid like you can run it up in no
time and we'd both be in the clear than
the glare anyway and maybe maybe
if I get caught. I could swear to
you you know when you're squeal Oh no not
squeal examined I like you man. Even if
you did tell the cops I was in on it with
you what did they do that may they might
give me the same medicine they gave you.
That Lee. Will be doing will be
rational All right I think the
eighteen fifteen you kick yourself on the
back of the GET AWAY FROM YOU TAKE THAT
CAN. Well another during your being
a good one that's when people wind up
behind the eightball once they get
a few dollars to become greedy and want
more. Freezer you know that Roman general
he got his for being greedy he wasn't
satisfied the final wind up once he took the
count a couple of days ago you didn't have
a dime of what you were so broke
you couldn't pay case for
a postage stamp now you've got almost seven
hundred dollars with eighteen fifty in
the offing take my advice don't try for
more in this game let's have some blackjack
for play solitaire camera that's the way
I feel about that's the way I feel about
it and so on the wrong things won't
help much rather I'm really doing you
a favor I'll be out of agenda keep my
mouth shut I'll show you how to make some
soft money and what the heck do I get right
now I'd rather call the cops and tell
them you killed
a man and so I did not I mean yes you do
you know I didn't you know I did and. Then
. I. Suppose I call the cops here in
this and what do you got to be scared of
OK. Go ahead in column C.
Of right here at least they'll give me
a square deal you want me to cause you
hurt me and I want you to find an instance
where you were going and I see that you
help me and find friends I could even with
you. Here and try to see. You.
OK.
And I mention. I want to know
the Hollywood police station.
OK I got
a tax. Credit for you wouldn't do that
well wouldn't that now show you if I
would take it easy now let's talk this
over this was early in the evening the
conversation while hectic was at least
pitched low. But as the minutes passed and
more obstacles to
a plan popped into my head the air got
blue each word coming from outlets cracked
like when. I reminded her that as
a child has come I didn't even know my
mother's name where I had gone to school and
they were my best friend when I had an Aunt
Em are not my religion and if I'd ever
owned
a dog I didn't even know what my middle
initial stood for I also pointed out that
the real Haskell had
a scar on his forearm his people never
saw that scary told me to run away right
after but not the kids I yeah but his father
knew it was cut it to be some kind of
a market so. The elements there will
be I hope by tomorrow morning's by
the way you know what got yourself
a little Cousin Jack. Though I have that
Canada Line on my leg off drunken you're
crazy mad for term if you want to but I
won't get mixed up on this but side of we
don't have to was such a phony It wasn't
a man's point at all maybe just dreamed
it up right then and you know well the
dream I won a lot on the shoulder in is
a cute little gas chamber waiting for you
grab it and I hear it from the can there
is all of this. What about the
GOING TO MAKE ME of Iraq I want to
believe. I hate you I think you'll
learn it I'll let you alone your
promise I made a phone worthy of your
trunk you know what you're doing hurt me
a promise. Right.
I'm sorry but they're cracking Iraq and I
believe that it's not high Don't tell me
not do you do or did you want to
work. Here or not Germans yes. All
right I'll open up the window. Cracked.
Open the door please open the door here
open the door don't use the phone listen to
me I don't like your advice your knowledge
announcing you have heard my head and
I'm going to get even with you you don't
open the door I'm going to kick it down
there are no I don't call the cops listen
to me do anything you're safe there let
me. Bring opponents.
The world is full of skeptics. I want
myself. In the Hesco business how
many of you would believe he fell out of
the car now after killing Sarah without
really meaning to do it how many of you
would believe it wasn't premeditated. In
a jury room every last man of you would
go down shouting and she had me over
a barrel and my only out which of
course. They're going to do. So
quiet that for
a while I wanted to find something on
death. It was pure fear of course and I was
hysterical. But the. Girl
was dead. And that was her
murder. Murder put it off
a word that is what I have become one and
then I get caught. What evidence there
was around the place had to be destroyed
from the looks of things I was plenty
looking around the room and things with
blood was like looking into the faces of
a hundred people seen us together and
who remembered me. This was the kind of
testimony I couldn't rub out. I could brand
clothes and hide bottles for the next
five years and always be witnesses the
landlady for one she could identify me the
cabbie was the waitress in the drive
and the girl in the crash happened
a kind of liquor store I figured
on identifying. I was cooking. For
I had to get out of there.
I once I remained beside
a good body and carefully how to avoid
being accused of killing him this time I
couldn't. This time I was
killed if. You look. Out.
I was like
a guy suffering from shock things were
running around in my head I couldn't make
myself think right. How could I think I
was the guy with the saxophone nobody was
playing. It was not a
love song and. It was
a true. If
my problems weren't saw. I had to stay away
from New York for all time. Because our
robbers was most of the staff at the state.
And I could never go back to Hollywood
. Someone might recognize me as
Haskell. Then too that was too.
I could never go to her with
a thing like this hanging over my head.
All I could do was pray she kept.
I was in Bakersfield before I read that
girl's body was discovered that the police
were looking for Haskell in connection
with his wife's murder. Isn't that
a laugh. Has got me into this mess and
Haskell is getting me out of what the police
were searching for
a dead man. I keep trying to
forget what happened. And
wonder what my life might have been
a set of car estos hadn't stopped. But
one thing I don't have to wonder about.
I know. Today
a car will stop to pick
me up but I never. Get
. Paid. A somewhat serious farce
and put the finger on you or
me. For no good reason at all.
With.